<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Openshift on sysadm.life</title>
    <link>https://sysadm.life/tags/openshift/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Openshift on sysadm.life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sysadm.life/tags/openshift/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing the Nvidia GPU Operator on Openshift 4</title>
      <link>https://sysadm.life/posts/openshift_nvidia_gpu_operator/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sysadm.life/posts/openshift_nvidia_gpu_operator/</guid>
      <description>A disconnected installation of the gpu-operator on Openshift is not officially documented. If you attempt to install the Operator disconnected the pods fail to run as they are unable to pull the required rpms to build the driver for the specific kernel version of the CoreOS node on which they are running on. The operator can therefore be made to work by hosting the required rpm packages in a local mirror.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modifying Openshifts CoreOS ignition files</title>
      <link>https://sysadm.life/posts/openshift_static_ip_dhcpd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sysadm.life/posts/openshift_static_ip_dhcpd/</guid>
      <description>This article was put together to help assist performing Openshift 4 deployments on VMWare ESXi where static IPs are required but where DHCP is available and is allowed to give out temporary addresses. Doing it this way as (opposed to my last article where DHCP was not used) allows us to use the ova templates and will not require the creation of any separate boot isos. This is possible as enabling DHCP will allow the machines that have been created with the just the OVAs to boot first using a random DHCP given IP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Openshift 4 on ESXi using Packet</title>
      <link>https://sysadm.life/posts/openshift_static_ip_disconnected_esxi_install/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sysadm.life/posts/openshift_static_ip_disconnected_esxi_install/</guid>
      <description>This article aims to present the steps required to create the minimum necessary infrastructure to install and gain familiarity with Openshift 4.4 on VMware ESXi (hosted on packet.com) using static IP addresses in a disconnected environment&amp;hellip; so a bit more than the standard run of the mill install!
So why did I choose this setup? Well, I chose to use Packet as they provide easily provisionable bare metal in the cloud that is reasonably priced and I&amp;rsquo;m hoping that if someone wanted to replicate this setup they could easily do so following the below steps.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>